therumpus.net 2019-03-30

# Privacy Policy - The Rumpus.net

##### Who we are:

Our website address is [http://therumpus.net](http://therumpus.net/).

##### What personal data we collect and why we collect it:

We do not collect personal data.

##### Embedded content from other websites:

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

##### Analytics:

The Rumpus uses Jetpack and Google Analytics. Data collected is anonymized.

##### **Who we share your data with:**

We do not share your data.

##### **What rights you have over your data:**

You can always request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes. To make this request, please email [marisa@therumpus.net](mailto:marisa@therumpus.net).

**Please visit our store at[store.therumpus.net](https://store.therumpus.net/) to view privacy policies related to store accounts and the store website.**

**For any questions or concerns about our privacy policy and your data please email  [marisa@therumpus.net](mailto:marisa@therumpus.net).**
